PROJECT TITLE: Fasty
PURPOSE OF PROJECT: Just for fun :)
VERSION: 2.0.2 
AUTHOR: Pop Alexandru Radu *** Get support here: minealex2244@gmail.com

***HOW TO START THIS PROJECT: Double-click on "project.greenfoot" and then 'Run'. IF ANY EXCEPTION OCCURS: Just delete res.txt file, run the project again and optionally click 'Reset' to input your name. This method will erase your data.

***USER INSTRUCTIONS: Radu has just got a new job: ambulance driver. But this is not as simple as it sounds. How fast are you to save the people? Please read README_RULES.TXT for more informations.

***HOTKEYS: Movement from arrows or WASD, P-pause, Q-use bonus powers.

***CREDITS: stackoverflow.com for an optimised properties loading and writing, Stoichiță Iulia Alexandra for giving me the idea to add a story ;)


*****  CHANGELOG  ***** 

*****pre 1.0*****

-initial game tests

*****v1.0*****

-made the game to be functional (to collect the boys)

*****v1.1*****

-possibility to see the saved boys

*****v1.2*****

-minor improvements of code

*****v1.3*****

-optimised the code (added properties management)

*****v1.4*****

-added levels
-added timer
-added username support
-added Game Over screen
-a lot of code and speed improvements

*****v1.5*****

-added WASD controls
-bugfixes for Game Over screen
-fixed the NullPointerException caused by Greenfoot
-other improvements

*****v1.6*****

-added the power to add max. 3 seconds (bonus gained from 10 to 10 levels)
-removed useless code lines
-fixed a bug which makes the level to show "0" and after you won it shows the real level

*****v1.7*****

-all the strings are now translated in English
-added obstacles

*****v1.8*****

-fixed obstacle-related bugs (also related to boys)
-fixed a bug which spawns the player right into the obstacle

*****v2.0.0*****

-new versioning (the last "0" is only for minor bugfixes releases)
-a new chance when hitting the buildings ;) 
-fixed a bug which lets you continue the game even if you won
-using Greenfoot Terminal to notify the user

*****v2.0.1*****

-fixed the no information bug (now, only needs to load)

*****v2.0.2*****

-hopefully fixed the object-in-building bug (building over building is NORMAL)
